System Specialist II

CONTACT

- **385 335 2909**
- Seth.Willardson@uvu.edu
- Vineyard | UT (relocating)
- Click for LinkedIn

SKILLS

Desktop Engineering

ITSM and Incident Management

Agile Methodology

Network Engineering

Organization

EDUCATION

BS/Information Technology Utah Valley University 2015-2021 Magna Cum Laude

CERTIFICATIONS

CompTIA A+ January 2019 CompTIA Network+ October 2021

REFERENCES

Aaron J.H. Barret – Systems Administrator III

<u>Aaron.Barrett@uvu.edu</u> 801-863-8946

Jordan Kratochvil – IT Support Administrator
Jordan K@uvu.edu 801-863-8141

ABOUT ME

Self-motivated Systems
Specialist eager to learn and improve in system
administration and networking.

My greatest achievements in my career are the positive, professional relationships I have built with my coworkers. I have valuable technical knowledge and experience from both education and 5 years in the field.

EXPERIENCE

System Specialist II

Utah Valley University | Orem, Utah | December 2020-Current

- Own the role of incident manager collaborating with SMEs and IT leadership to identify improvements after incidents.
- Perform Atlassian administrative tasks and development.
- Assist in NOC tasks including data center maintenance, systems monitoring, and on-call alerting.

Support Technician III

Utah Valley University | Orem, Utah | December 2016-December 2020

- With a ticketing system, collaborated with end-users via inperson and remotely to troubleshoot and solve technical issues.
- Assisted in managing Windows and Mac system deployment.
- Provided written instruction and technical documentation.

Business Systems Software Tester

Studies Weekly | Orem, Utah | December 2015 – August 2016

- Performed quality assurance and assisted in change management for agile improvements to business software.
- Documented, troubleshot, and collaborated with developers to fix software bugs or unintentional behavior.